Hello, welcome to AT News Swadesh.
You are watching
our special show Mid Cap Masala on mid cap stocks and
with you I am Abhishek Satyavratam.
After seven consecutive sessions of rise in the market,
consolidation is visible today and the April series is
also expiring today, hence there is a
slightly volatile environment in the market.
However, Nifty is currently trading with a weakness of only 70 points.
Is around 24,250.
But after losing 250 points yesterday,
today we see that Nifi Bank is trying to recover
in the beginning.  But it is flat right now.
Trading is taking place at a slight decline of 89 points.
Nifty or Bank is around 55350.  The
question is
what should be your strategy in the market?  Is it a
market for buy on dips only?  Is this a good level to
enter?
What are the support levels for Nifty?  Do you have your
stop loss for Nifty?  Should it be
around 24,000?  Many questions will be
in your mind.  But since it is a mid-cap show, let me
tell you about the situation of mid-cap.
Relatively speaking,
Nifty Midcap 100 and Nifty Smallcap
100 will perform slightly better than Nifty today
and that is also visible in the advance decline ratio.
Today, around 150 stocks are trading strong
and 1000 stocks are
trading weak and the reason for this is that
you will see small cap candies trading half a percent higher at the
moment.  India is
up around 2.5-3% around 16 1/2.
But today
you will see cement stocks supporting the market.
Ultratech and Grasim are bullish today.
Some select consumption stocks are also providing
support today and
we are seeing that strength remains in pharma.
Sun Pharma, SPL, Dr. Redes are some of the
stocks which are seeing a rise today.  Ah
but HL yes the results primafc looked like it was
okay but the stock lost 4%.  We will
discuss about this today.  But
another stock in Syngen Mid Cap where we
saw a sharp decline.  We will talk about Syngen and
Thyro is running at a very fast pace in the mid today
because the margins
of Thyro Care have come out very strong.  So the
focus will be on all these shares.  But first let us bring three
pictures which will give us an idea of ​​the
mid cap environment.  So, due to
weak results of the engine, the stock slips by 11% and the
reason for this is that the profits have fallen.
Margins have also seen pressure.  But
somewhere the share is becoming a victim of over reaction.
Tata Group company Rallis has reported
widening losses in Q4.  Income has decreased by about 18%.
But this stock reached from 200 to 250 by showing a one-sided
journey.  So a little bit of
profit taking is coming today.  Dalmia Bharat
rose nearly 4% on strong results, with
strong revenue growth and volumes in Q4.
So we will
discuss these three pictures regarding these three shares further.
But meanwhile, quoting sources,
see the news that the government has
advised aviation companies not to use Pakistan's airspace.
So the
government has taken this decision from the security point of view
and let us tell you that yesterday when PM Modi
returned from his Saudi Arabia tour midway,
he also did not use Pakistan's airspace.
While leaving,
he used Pakistan's airspace.
But while coming he
came from a different route.  So these are all the things
in the context of the Pahalgam attack.  We
saw that the government
put a lot of pressure on Pakistan.  Many restrictions were imposed.   The
government also rejected the Indus Water Treaty.
After that it was
decided to close the Attari Wagah border.
Told the people of Pakistan to
leave India within 2 days, many things are going on.  A
series of meetings is also to be held regarding this.  An
all-party meeting is also to be held today.
Led by Defence Minister Rajnath Singh.  Let's see
what comes out of it.  So
this tension remains.  We are also keeping an eye on this.
But let's connect with our experts
and understand from them what
your strategy should be in the market.  3 hours have
passed.  3 hours of session still to go
and join us today to guide you.
Amol Aathwale of Kotak Securities is a veteran expert.  Amol ji,
thank you very much for your time.
Welcome to ATAZ.  Let's get the show
started.  Let us understand the view of Nifty once.  Let's
create an index strategy.
After that we will discuss further.
First, Nifty's 3-hour trend.
Some good news regarding Amol tariff,
short covering, all these things
fueled the market that led to a seven day one-
sided rally in Nifty of around 2000 points.
Today it seems to be getting a little slowed down.
Now the new series will start from tomorrow.
Today, please tell me
that if there is a dip of 70-80 points, say 100 points, then should we
enter there or should we wait a little,
what should we do in the market for the next three hours in Nifty?  Yes, I think the
intraday view will be a little negative.
Weakness may increase a little more.  But
definitely if you
get an intraday deep as you said 241 is an
important support level.  If
the market corrects to that extent, then definitely a
buying approach will remain from a positional point of view.  At
present, if you look at it on a 3-hour basis, as long as the
market is
trading below 24,300, I think this
intraday weak sentiment
seems to be continuing somewhere.
This is the view regarding Nifty.
Prime Minister Modi has reached Madhubani in Bihar.  I will
address a gathering there shortly.  We are keeping an eye on him.
As soon as his speech starts, we will take you there
and this is important
because after the attack on Pahalgam, this is the first time that
PM Modi is making a public address from any platform,
so it will be very crucial.  You have to
see and hear.  Let's go straight there
and listen to what PM Modi is saying.   On the
occasion of Panchayati Raj Day, the
entire
country is connected with Mithila.  It
is connected to Bihar.  Today, the foundation stone and inauguration of
projects worth thousands of crores of rupees related to the development of Bihar in the country has taken place here.
These various works related to electricity, railways and infrastructure will
create new employment opportunities in Bihar.
Today is also the
death anniversary of national poet Ramdhari Shri Dinkar ji.
I pay my
humble tribute to him.
Friends, Bihar is the land
from where revered Bapu had
spread the mantra of Satyagraha.
Respected Bapu firmly believed
that unless the
villages of India become strong,
India will not be able to develop rapidly.
This is the spirit behind the concept of Panchayati Raj in the country.
In the last decade, one step after another was taken to empower the Panchayats.
Panchayats were also strengthened through technology.
In the last decade, more than two lakh gram panchayats have been
connected to the internet.
More than 5 lakh Common Service
Centres were built in villages.   There has been
another benefit from the Panchayats going digital.
Many documents like life and death certificate, land holding certificate etc. can be
obtained easily.
Where the country got a
new Parliament building after many decades of independence.
new Panchayat buildings were also built in the country.
Panchayats should
get adequate funds.
This has also been a priority of the government.
In the last 10 years,
Panchayats have received funds worth more than ₹ lakh crore.  All this
money is invested in the development of the village.
Friends,
another major
problem of Gram Panchayats has been related to land dispute.
Which
land
is inhabited?  Which farming have you done
?  Which is the Panchayat land
?  What is government land?  And there is
often controversy on all these issues,
so PM Modi is in Madhubani, Bihar.
This program is organized on National Panchayati Day
and there PM Modi will launch infrastructure projects worth
approximately Rs 13000 crore from this platform.  He will
flag off the train and
PM Modi also expressed grief over the Pahalgam attack
and said that
we pay tribute to those who died.  If something else important
comes out from there then we will take you again to
this meeting of PM Modi in Madhubani
but let's return to the market.  Amol
is fine.  We have understood your view on Nifty.
Now tell me,
where do you think the opportunities are being created in stocks?
Where will you trade?  What will you buy?   I would like to
go with ICICI GI.
I took it from a positional point of view.
Picked around 1878.  Positional targets are coming out to be
2000 and its stop loss will be
18838.  There
is a fairly stable uptrend.  Consistently higher highs and
higher lows are being formed in stocks.
If there was a big resistance which was 1850
in the stock, after crossing the same the stock is
trading comfortably above it.
I think overall, if we
look at the momentum, it is on the positive side and the
chances of it continuing are visible on the charts.
Second I would like to go with Koro Mandala.  It
is around 2245.  Positional
target is coming out to be ₹2360 and
its stop loss will be ₹2200.  Consistently the
stock is in higher high higher loss formation.   There is
not much pressure of correction in any stock.  A stable up trend has been maintained.
I think that this up trend
continuation formation is
likely to continue in the coming days as seen on the
charts.
Ok.  Coromandel, which is a fertilizer
related company, has a target of ₹2360 and a
stop loss of ₹2200 and the
country also recommends buying ICC PDL.   So there
you have it, two bullish stocks.  Ah,
meanwhile this news will come, we will look into it that
after the Pahalgam attack, the government has advised domestic
airlines not to use Pakistan's airspace.
A
while ago our ticket team was flashing this news to you.  Let us get
some
detailed information on this.  Our
colleague Sameer Dixit has joined us.
Sameer, definitely it was bound to happen,
even PM Modi did not use that route
when he was returning from Saudi Arabia.   Can
you tell me what guidelines have been issued
for airlines?
Yes, let me tell you that the
major decisions taken by the government after the Pahalgam attack will be taken
after the meeting of the CCS Cabinet Committee on Security.  So now the government is
taking all the precautionary steps which
are necessary for safety and in the same direction, sources are telling
that now the government or rather the Civil
Aviation Ministry can soon issue a Not Time
Notice to Airmen.
This will be an advisory.
This will be an instruction for the country's airlines that
they should not use Pakistan's airspace at such a sensitive time.
Avoid this.
So the government can issue this instruction or this advisory
soon.  Not
released yet.  But sources say that
it can be released soon.  And this will be
for all those
airlines of India which currently mostly
head towards Gulf countries.
This will be a very important advisory for those who take the route to Gulf countries like Muscat or Middle East countries that
if they do not use Pakistan's airspace, then
if they have to avoid it and
go, they will have to take this diversion of about half an hour.  There
is definitely a cost implication in this because the
airlines also incur the same fuel cost.  But
from the security point of view and
considering the current sensitive situation, the government
can issue this advisory in which the
airlines of the country can be told, this note can be
issued by the government that
they should not use the airspace of Pakistan for the time being.  Let us
tell you that a similar
situation had arisen earlier also
when the Balakot strike took place in Pulwama, even then
a similar advisory was issued by the government
that the airlines of the country should
avoid Pakistan airspace and even now the airspace which is being
used is very partially, very less
time is being used but
still understanding the situation the government can
issue such an advisory.  Yes, it
is okay Sameer, thank you very much for this information. If we
look at it,
it is definitely a little negative for the aviation companies because there will be
more fuel expenditure, but
this decision has been taken in the national interest and we are seeing that
since yesterday,
our Aviation Minister Naidu Saheb Rammohan
Naidu has been very active. He has taken many decisions back to back for the
passengers who are leaving Kashmir and the
tourists who want to leave from there.
He also asked airlines
not to do search pricing.  Keep the fare normal
so that people can be comfortable.
Some instructions also came from DGCA to provide convenience to the airlines there.
So these things are happening
and these developments are continuously taking place
in the context of this news.  Come on, it's
time for a short break.
When we return after the break, we will look at some more big
news and try to
understand some more good trades for you through Amol.
You stay with us.
Welcome back to Mid
Cap Masala after the break.  The market is trading in a range
and when we started the Nifty show, it was
down by 70 points.  Now you will see
57 58 numbers below.  So there
is a market of range only.  Meanwhile,
breaking news is coming regarding BHEL that there is a
fire in the company's Bhopal plant.
This stock is down by 1.5%.  Yesterday also we
saw some pressure in BHEL shares.  It
is a capital goods company and BHEL has
a plant near MP Nagar in Bhopal.  Let's
see what
comes out of it.
But let's move ahead and now let's talk about
another mid-cap company which is
related to the diagnostic space and that
company is Thyro.
We are seeing a great session today after the results of Thyro Care and this
stock has reached an 8-month high
and has almost completely compensated for the fall of this year i.e.
2025.  Only
4-5% distance would be left.  So
why is Thayer experiencing this boom?
What is so special about the results that has given the stock so much enthusiasm
?  Let us understand this.  Our colleague
Ravindra has joined us.  Ravindra
Excellent session, some profit checking from higher levels
but still
above 13%.  Tell me why is
this share running?
Yes, absolutely, Thayer's stock is in focus today.
Where the company announced its earnings for Q4
and the company's revenue has
seen a growth of 21% on
year-on-year basis.  And if we talk about
PET, then a good growth is being seen in PET also.
If we talk about
EBITDA, then the EBITDA of the company is
seen increasing from Rs 34 crore to Rs 58 crore.  The
margins are seen increasing from 21.9% to
30.8%.
Overall, the company's earnings for Q4 are
quite strong.  If we talk about
volume, then in Q4, there has been a
growth of 11% on year on year
basis.  And if we talk about segment
wise performance, then the company's
franchise business segment has
seen a growth of 22%.  At the same time, there has been a
growth of 23% in pathology revenue on
year on year basis.   The
company is expanding rapidly by leveraging inorganic growth opportunities such as company acquisitions
and is focused on
remaining a B2B service provider with a
cost-effective value base model
that will benefit large-scale operations.
Thyrog is strengthening its current franchise
and the company is
also rapidly expanding in Tanzania
which will provide
reliable, high quality and affordable
diagnostic testing services and the
acquisitions that the company made in FI 25 were Polo
Lab and Vimta Lab where the company's aim was to
expand its footprint in North India and Andhra Pradesh and Telangana, the
performance of these acquisitions has
started showing in Q4 where the
inorganic growth in Q4 was 2%.  Along with
this, some brokerage
notes are also coming on Thyro where Incret has
issued its note on Thyro and they have maintained the
add rating and target price
which is 1010 where they have
added the stock in high convention idea and they say that the stock
provides a suitable entry point.
He says that the company's earnings in Q4 have been
quite good and
Tanjana is at a next nsecant stage.
But the revenue is
doubling quarter on quarter and he
says that Thyrocare can continue its acquisition in FI 26 as part of its
growth strategy, due to which,
due to strong q for earnings, a
good rise is being seen in the stocks.
Ok?  Excellent earnings,
especially if you look at the margins, the
margins have gone above 30% and the
view of brokerage houses is also quite bullish.  Incred
says that this stock can go up to ₹110,
their target is around ₹870.  So
from here also good upside is
seen in Incred's share.  Amol ji, a quick
view of your thyroid.  What do you think
about the stock?  There has been a very sharp bounce back.
If we look at this week so far, there has been a
rally of 22%.  But one important thing has
definitely happened that the stock has comfortably crossed the 200 day simple
moving average today.  At
present, trading is happening on that only.
Volume activity that
is incremental.  I think maybe we might see some consolidation for a day or two.
But the 200 day
simple moving average will
be a tolerant level which
comes around 820 and remains above it, so the chances of this
bullish setup continuing from the positional point of view are
visible on the charts.
Look Amol Bhai, thank you very much for giving your time
in this show today and for
guiding us about mid cap stocks and
also for telling us the best trading strategies,
but know